mscgva.ch 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy | MSC

This is a website operated by MSC Mediterranean Shipping Company S.A (hereinafter called "MSC" or "we"). MSC is registered in Switzerland at 12-14 Chemin Rieu 1208, Geneva.

MSC is committed to ensure that your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy accounts for the personal information collected, processed and used via this website.

By using this website, you agree on the collection, the use and the disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this policy.

If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, please refrain from visiting this site.

#### What information we collect

On our website, the information collected will depend on which of our services you utilize. Most of our services do not require any form of registration, allowing you to visit our site without telling us who you are. However, some of them may require you to provide us with personal information. In these situations, the sort of personal information requested will generally include but shall not be limited to the name, the postal address, the email address or the telephone number.

#### Uses made of the information

We use the information about you in the following ways:

  * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes
  * to process your requests and inquiries
  * to process your online job application

We will not sell, share, transfer or use the information we collect through this website for other purposes than the above stated.

#### How we collect your personal information

The information will be collected and stored in good faith, in a proportionate manner, for the purposes above indicated and with the appropriate technical and organizational measures in line with the state of art, the risks represented by the processing and the nature of the data protected.

#### Disclosure of the information

We may disclose your personal information to other MSC’s agents worldwide or to third parties who act for or on our behalf. These are required to treat the information only for the purpose for which is provided and in accordance with this Privacy policy.

We may also disclose your information to a third party if we are required to do so because of an applicable law, court order or governmental regulation, or if such disclosure is otherwise necessary in support any criminal or legal investigation or proceeding.

#### Data transfer abroad

The information submitted to us may be transferred and processed for the purposes described above in locations outside the country in which you are viewing this website, potentially including countries which may not require an adequate level of protection for your personal data compared with that provided in your country. By accepting this Privacy Policy you consent to the transfers as described in this section.

#### Links

Our website may, from time to time, contain links to and from websites of our partner’s networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to the websites.

#### Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log on information and visitor behavior. The information is used to track visitor use of the website to compile statistical report on the website activity. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. Please note that in a few cases some of our website features may not function if you remove the cookies from your browser. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes we use them, you may consult our Cookie policy.

#### Right of access, correction and objection

You are entitled to ask us for information about what type of personal data about you has been collected online. You may also ask to have your data rectified or deleted as required by applicable law. For more information please contact us using details in the contact section below.

#### Changes

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make. The Privacy Policy published on our website is kept up to date.

#### Contact

If you have any queries or you wish to exercise your rights under applicable legislation such as what type of personal data has been collected, you may contact us by sending a letter to the following address: [datarequest@msc.com. ](mailto:datarequest@msc.com?cc=ch001-data.protection@msc.com&subject=Customer%20Data%20Request%20-%20from%20MSC.com)

Corporate Legal Department  
MSC Mediterranean Shipping Company S.A  
12-14 Chemin Rieu  
1208 Geneva  
Switzerland
